我踩下油门，看整车人都像个笑话
put my foot on the gas see the whole carjoke
我根本不玩那些体育破事
I ain't even playing in sports shit
金库没读出我的码，我会去犯罪
gold cells ain't reading my rats I'll commit the crime
谁在乎法律怎么说
who cares what the law said
对我隔壁邻居胡说八道
SO crap to my next door neighbor
我他妈才不管那些垃圾堆在我家门口
I don't give a fuck all shit on my doorstep
没心情
not in a mood
我的杯子刚洒了
on my cup just spilled
打碎了，我需要全套新的
hit broke like I need me a full set foolish
我真傻所有孩子都上私立学校
all my kids got private schooling
我住带游泳池的房子
and I live in a house with a pool
花园很大，还养马
and the garden big got horses
我把其中一个房间弄得完美无瑕
I made one of my chamber flawless
嗨到我不知道这是几楼
so high I don't know what floor this is
税交了，还订了货
taxes paid and ordered it
那辆Black Badge库里南我订的
the Black Badge Collie I ordered it
26年款
26 plate
看，一切都是最新规格，跟那些邪恶的年轻人待着
look everything new spec stay with some devilish youth
一步走错，你可能
step one foot wrong and you might
就会出现在新闻片段里
end up on a news clip
我没妄想，我知道同样的事也可能发生在我身上
I ain't delusional I know the same can happen to me
BREAKING NEWS 我没妄想会我知道同样的事也可能发生在我身上
我没妄想，我知道同样的事也可能发生在我身上
如果我松懈了
if I'm loosened
转变，切断那些关系
switch up and cut off the loose ends
我像拉弦一样扣动，像吉他
I'm pulling a string like acoustic
别diss我，然后说那是音乐
don't diss me and then say that it's music
找回场子，找借□
count back track and make excuses
你疯了吗，哥们给了你蓝图
are you mad man gave you the blueprint
授人与渔
take the horse to the water and tell man drink
我试过了，但它还是没用
I tried but it still don't do shit
我告诉人早上联系
Itold man link in the morning
告诉他9点，那家伙还在打盹
told him at 9 and the guy still snoozing
谈论妞们
talk about hoes
她们一听我谈工作
they hear anytime that I talk about the work
就不听了
don't tune in
我来自老地方
I'm from where the old is grooming
年轻男孩天真又无知
young boys naive and clueless
一开始是善意
it starts with nice
给点时间，同样男孩就会为开枪而嗨
give it some time same boys get higher for shooting
从外面看，他们看起来很风光，所以想
from the outside then they look lit so they wanna
成为那运动的一部分
your m be part of the movement
所以你躺在地板上，伤口敞开
so you're lying on the floor with an open wound
现在你淡化恩怨，稀释它
now you water the beef diluting
在钱路上，我不能绕道
on the paper route and I can't detour
直接飞过
fly straight through any diversion
死忠，我不想死时紧张
die hard I don't wanna die nervous
我的金不埋我的收入
my gold don't bury my earnings
对我来说没什么，我买包
it's nothing to me I buy purses
我女人有大概4、5个铂金包
my bitch got like 4 or 5 burkins
她想穿小黑裙出去吃，但我今晚忙
she wanna go out to eat on an LBD but I'm busy tonight
我在工作
I'm working
他们会把善意当软弱，所以我是恶魔
they'll take kindness forweakness I'm a demon
我是故意的
I did it on purpose
那外科医生的身体被买下，蒙特利尔俱乐部
that surgeon body get purchased Club Montreal
看到两个潜伏的
see two of them lurking
飞过几个负担 那个德国人
got flying up through a few burden that one German
OFTENANCY
飞过几个负担 那个德国人
飞过几个负担，那个德国人
那是你的负担
that's your burden
没排练
no rehearsing
拉开帷幕，当然我有专业知识
pull back the curtain certainly I got expertise
我最烦的是得到和平
my pet peeve is getting on peace
如果你凌晨3点出现
if you pull up at 3 in the morning
我不想说话，婊子
I don't wanna talk bitch
跪下，被抓
get on your knees caught
我有点惊讶
Iwas kinda surprised
不喜欢喝酒 但你怎么永远不会离开
won't like how 40 you never would leave
干了24/7
done2470t
没休息，现在我说话没意义
no rest now don't make sense when I speak
但管它呢，我睡时一切都死了
but fuck it all dead when I sleep
我是说，我死时才睡
I mean I sleep when I'm dead
是我开始还是我言出必行
did I start or I mean whatI said
我去和团队分钱
I go and break team in the bread
我是说我去和团队分面包
I mean I go and break bread with the team
我的兄弟闹了场然后跑了
my dog made a scene then fled
你的老板告诉我谁告密了
your boss tell me who have you fed
16岁变了，但没变甜
turned 16 but nothing went sweet
没年轻她，那我就代替做
no young she then do it instead
我和小兄弟像可卡因和快克
me and lil bro like coke and crack
两辆双R，现在我们滚动如石
2 double R's now we rolling stone
但有一阵子偷过宠物
but for a while it was stolen pets
噩梦让我出最冷的汗
nightmares gave me the coldest sweats
醒来以为一切都是梦
woke up and I thought it was all a dream
但真兄弟死了
but it's real bro really is dead sick
忘了睡了多久
lost track how long have I slept
我吃的这些药导致记忆丧失，但我依旧想忘记
these pulls pop give memory loss butI wanna forget
你好吗，还是你看起来不爽
are you good or you seem upset
我要“人头”湿，脖子干净
Iwant heads wet clean off necks
钱不能治愈压力
the money's not healing stress
我需要能量，性爱
I need energy female sex
我需要诚实意见
I need honest opinions
拜托，我不想听你同意说对
please I don't wanna hear you agree and say yes
你不必努力， 但你在欺骗自己
you ain't gotta work hard but you're cheating yourself
你在选更容易的代表
you're choosing the easier rep
当G问你代表谁
when the G's ask who do you rep
你会挺胸说，还是低声下气
will you say with chest or under your breath
有权保持沉默，或一旦我说话
have the right to remain silent or once did I speak
在被捕时
when under arrest
在脱衣舞俱乐部是轻松的一天
it's a light day in a strip club
如果我走进去花不到10个
if I walk in spent under 10
TIMES SQUARE
我说唱只为了赚钱
Ionly rap cause wanna get paid
我不想成为最棒的之一
I don't wanna be one of the best
年轻时有过彩笔，这些Z世代坏男孩
as a youth had color and pens these Gen Z bad boys
我让宝贝们看到我全神贯注
I've had babies see me put all my eyes on wavy
你想知道我花了多少时间装成熟
you wanna know how much time it took me acting fully
心曾是恶霸
the heart was bully
我投入了一班，慢跑
I put in a shift Ijog as a Jovie
谁都能欺负弱者，那没啥意思
anybody can pray on the weak that's cheating on Chi
我们欺负恶霸
we bully the bullies